belvoir.com 2003-06-02

# Belvoir -Privacy Page

**Belvoir Publications, Inc. Privacy Policy  
**

**Belvoir** is a company solely dedicated to serving the needs of its readers. And we are deeply committed to protecting your privacy and security when you access **Belvoir** owned web sites.We believe you have the right to know everything regarding the information we collect about you as you use our web sites...how this information benefits you...and how you can say "no" to the use of any of the information. 

Belvoir Publications has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to protecting your privacy and security. By using this site, you indicate your acceptance of Belvoir Publications' Online Privacy Policy. 

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible).   
**  
What Information is Collected **  
We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. 

**How We Use the Information**  
The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes, as well as fulfill customer's orders. 

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on our products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by sending us an e-mail at the above address. Please provide us with the publication you subscribe to as well as your exact name and address. 

You may also receive mailings from other reputable companies. You can, however, have your name put on our do-not-share list by sending us an e-mail at the above address. Please provide us with the publication you subscribe to as well as your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations.

If you supply us with your email address, you may receive periodic emails from us. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address. Please provide us with the publication you subscribe to as well as your exact name and address. 

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line. 

**We do not share email addresses or telephone numbers with other organizations.**  
  
**Cookies and How They are Used**  
Cookies are tiny pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are set when "Shopping Cart" is in use. This allows us to keep track of your current transaction during the order taking process. We use cookies for Shopping Cart, but we do not store personally identifiable information in your cookie.  
**  
Changes **  
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by sending us e-mail at the above address. 

**We Do Not Partner With or Have Special Relationships With Any Ad Server Companies.**

**How You Can Access or Correct Information**  
Upon request we provide site visitors with access to transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by e-mailing us at the above address. 

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in all information that we maintain. Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address.

**Security**  
We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. 

**If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above address or phone number.**
